Guide to the Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection 1977-2002 MSS 128
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XII: Vinyl Sound Recordings
  - Subseries D: Vinyl Recordings - Various Poets
    - Lenny Bruce, "I am Not a Nut, Elect Me!; Fantasy (Box 41)
    - The Real Lenny Bruce; Fantasy (Box 41)
    - Lenny Bruce, The Berkeley Concert Two Record Set; Reprise Records (Box 41)
    - Lord Buckley, Blowing His Mind (and Yours Too); World Pacific (Box 41)
    - The Best of Lord Buckley; Elektra (Box 41)
    - Kenneth Patchen Reads His Poetry with the Chamber Jazz Sextet; Cadence (Box 41)
    - Kenneth Rexroth; Fantasy (Box 41)
    - Poetry Readings in the Cellar with the Cellar Jazz Quintet: Kenneth Rexroth, Lawrence Ferlinghetti; Fantasy (Box 41)
    - Douglas Moore, The Devil and Daniel Webster; Westminster Hi-Fi Long Play Records (Box 41)
    - Wilfred Owen (1893-1918), Richard Johnson as Wilfred Owen with Tony Church, Frank Duncan, Edited by Frederick Woods; Argo (Box 41)
    - The Poetry and Voice of James Wright; Caedmon (Box 41)
    - E.E. Cummings Reads His Poetry; Caedmon (Box 41)
    - E.E. Cummings Reads His Poetry; Caedmon (Box 41)
    - The Poetry of Carl Sandberg; Caedmon (Box 41)
    - Robert Frost Reads His Poetry; Caedmon (Box 41)
    - Carl Sandburg Reading Fog and Other Poems; Caedmon (Box 41)
    - Ernest Hemingway Reading; Caedmon (Box 41)
    - T.S. Eliot Reading Poems and Choruses; Caedmon (Box 41)
  - Subseries E: Vinyl Recordings - Allen Ginsberg
    This group of Allen Ginsberg recordings was purchased at an October 1999 Sotheby's auction by Bob Holman.
    - Auction Materials, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents note
      This folder holds Bob Holman's receipt and invoice from Sotheby's detailing his purchase of the materials in subseries E along with a copy of the auction catalog ("Allen Ginsberg and Friends") and a newspaper clipping regarding the auction: Edward Sanders, "The Beats on the Block," The New York Times, October 3, 1999, p. 17.
    - The John Cooper Clarke Airplay Sampler; CBS Records (Box 42)
    - Barry Wallenstein, Cecil McBee, Stanley Cowell, Beast Is; AK BA Records (Box 42)
    - Krack House; Shimmy Disc (Box 42)
    - Richard Hell and the Voidoids, Blank Generation; Sire (Box 42)
    - You're a Hook, The 15 Year Anniversary of Dial-a-Poem (1968-1983) (Box 42)
    - The Dial-a-Poem Poets, Disconnected; Giorno Poetry Systems (Box 42)
    - Janet Baker and Gerald Moore, A Pageant of English Song (1597-1961); His Master's Voice (Box 42)
    - The Twentieth Anniversary of the Summer of Love; Shimmy Disc (Box 42)
    - Start, Look Around; Fresh Sounds, Inc. (Box 42)
    - Allen Ginsberg, The Lion for Real; Great Jones (Box 42)
    - Ginsberg's Thing; Douglas Recording Corp. (Box 42)
    - A Pause in the Disaster, A Satire of the Conception Corporation; Cotillion (Box 42)
    - Made Up in Texas; Paris Records (Box 42)
    - Allen Ginsberg and Hobo Blues Band, Uvoltes (Howl); Krem (Box 42)
    - Tuli Kupferberg, Tuli and Friends; Shimmy Disc (Box 42)
    - The Clash, Combat Rock; Epic (Box 42)
    - Quarterly; Student Government Association of Montclair State College (Box 42)
    - Robert Johnson, King of the Delta Blues Singers; Columbia Records (Box 42)
    - Songs of Innocence and Experience by William Blake, Tuned by Allen Ginsberg; MGM Records (Box 42)
    - Allen Ginsberg Reads Kaddish, A 20th Century American Ecstatic Narrative Poem; Atlantic (Box 42)
    - Allen Ginsberg, First Blues; John Hammond Records (Box 42)
    - Allen Ginsberg, First Blues; John Hammond Records (Box 42)
    - Allen Ginsberg, First Blues; John Hammond Records (Box 42)
    - The Jack Kerouac Collection; Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 42)
      Format: Audiocassette HX Pro B NR
    - The Jack Kerouac Collection; Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 42)